<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">

    <string name="app_name">Happyworx SR Demo</string>

    <string name="start_screen_caption_en"></string>
    <string name="I_heared_caption">I heared : </string>
    <string name="preparingRecognizer_caption">Preparing Recognizer \n\n Please Wait...</string>
    <string name="btn_set_easteregg_back">Set and Back</string>
    <string name="info_screen_text">\n\nHappyworx Speech Recognition Demo\n\n

This demo was programmed as a Proof of Concept for Pocketsphinx in context of a reading app for children.\n\n

In this demo, Pocketsphinx is used in combination with the VoxForge language model for the Dutch language.
To learn more about Pocketsphinx, visit \n\n http://cmusphinx.sourceforge.net/ \n\n To learn more about VoxForge, visit \n\n
www.voxforge.org.\n\n

If you want to know more about the HappyWorx initiative, please go to our FaceBook page or visit www.happyworx.nl.
\n\n
The following disclaimer applies to the Pocketsphinx implementation :
\n\n
Copyright © 2014 Alpha Cephei Inc.  All rights reserved.
\n\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
\n\n
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
\n\n
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
\n\n
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY ALPHA CEPHEI INC. AS IS AND
ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL CARNEGIE MELLON UNIVERSITY
NOR ITS EMPLOYEES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</string>

    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-8205015694325849/9405387215</string>


</resources>