<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">

    <string name="app_name">Happyworx SR Demo</string>

    <string name="start_screen_caption_en"></string>
    <string name="I_heared_caption">Ik hoorde : </string>
    <string name="preparingRecognizer_caption">Spraakherkenning voorbereiden\n\n Even wachten aub...</string>
        <string name="info_screen_text">\n\nHappyworx Speech Recognition Demo\n\n

Deze demo is ontwikkeld als een Proof of Concept van Pocketsphinx in de context van een leren-lezen applicatie voor kinderen.\n\n
In deze demo wordt Pocketsphinx gebruikt in combinatie met het VoxForge language model voor de Nederlandse taal.
Als je meer wilt weten over Pocketsphinx, suft dan naar \n\n http://cmusphinx.sourceforge.net/ \n\n Wil je meer weten over Voxforge? Bezoek dan \n\n
www.voxforge.org.\n\n

Happyworx maakt apps voor android. Wil je meer weten over Happyworx? Bezoek dan www.happyworx.nl, of klik op de button hierboven.
\n\n
Hieronder vind je de copyright-notice van Pocketsphinx :
\n\n
Copyright © 2014 Alpha Cephei Inc.  All rights reserved.
\n\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
\n\n
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
\n\n
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
\n\n
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY ALPHA CEPHEI INC. AS IS AND
ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL CARNEGIE MELLON UNIVERSITY
NOR ITS EMPLOYEES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    </string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-8205015694325849/9405387215</string>
</resources>